Radix UP221
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Radix
2001 -- 2004
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP221
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Radix, a Tufts publication expressing the various politically liberal viewpoints of Tufts students.
- Radix, 2001 -- 2004; UP221.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Radix, a Tufts publication expressing the various politically liberal viewpoints of Tufts students.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Radix, 2001-12; UP221.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2002-02; UP221.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Radix, Gaypril, 2002-04; UP221.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2001-11; UP221.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2002-10; UP221.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2002-12; UP221.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2003-02; UP221.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2003-03; UP221.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2003-05; UP221.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2003-10; UP221.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2003-12; UP221.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Radix, 2004-04; UP221.001.001.00012 (Box 1)